<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Devflection</title>
    <link>https://devflection.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Devflection</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>matija@devflection.com (Matija Heričko)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>matija@devflection.com (Matija Heričko)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 08:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://devflection.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection in Java</title>
      <link>https://devflection.com/posts/2019-04-18-reflection-in-java/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>matija@devflection.com (Matija Heričko)</author>
      <guid>https://devflection.com/posts/2019-04-18-reflection-in-java/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Reflection is the ability of an application to inspect &lt;b&gt;and&lt;/b&gt; modify the code in the system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If an application can only inspect but not also modify the code then it only has the ability of introspection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So for an application to be reflective it must also be able to modify its code at runtime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://devflection.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>matija@devflection.com (Matija Heričko)</author>
      <guid>https://devflection.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Matija Heričko, I am a 27 year old software developer from Slovenia, currently living in Zürich in the beautiful country of Switzerland. A proud father of one very lively son, husband to a lovely wife and a very enthusiastic basketball player.
I started this blog to learn more by teaching, become a better software developer and hopefully along the way help other software developers also become better at their profession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book reviews</title>
      <link>https://devflection.com/page/book-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>matija@devflection.com (Matija Heričko)</author>
      <guid>https://devflection.com/page/book-reviews/</guid>
      <description>General Code complete 2 Code complete is another book that is extremely valuable and is probably one of the classics in the field. This book is a must read for any developer that wants to improve on their craft. It offers a lot of advice on writing more robust, maintainable, readable, better architected and overall more effective and efficient code. It is one of the best books on programming that exist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>